&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们确保我们完全清楚这个未定义的整体
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's make sure we're fully clear on this whole undefined
对未申报的东西。
versus undeclared thing.
可能会对你们中的一些人进行审查，但让我们确保我们完全清楚。
Might be review for some of you but let's just make sure we're fully clear.
未定义和未声明之间的区别是什么？
What is the difference between undefined and undeclared?
有人吗？
Anyone?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：您正在声明此变量存在，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're declaring this variable exist,
我没有给它赋值，但它存在。
I'm not assigning it a value but it exist.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，这是真的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, that's true.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：这里声明了但没有定义。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So there it's declared but not defined.
凯尔·辛普森：好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：未声明。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Undeclared.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，这是其中的一部分，你在正确的轨道上，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, that's part of it, you're on the right track but
还没完呢。
that's not all of it yet.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：未声明的在此期间从未分配过内存
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Undeclared has have never had the memory allocated during
编译器解析阶段而未定义。
the compiler parsing stage whereas undefined.
也许它被分配了，但从来没有分配给它的值。
Maybe it was allocated but there's never been a value assigned to that.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：将两者
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Putting both of
把你的答案放在一起，我们就能得到完整的答案。
your answers together we can get the complete answer.
让我重申一下。
So let me restate that.
你们都是对的。
You are both correct.
你在正确的轨道上，所以让我重申这一点。
You're on the right track so let me restate this.
这两者之间的差异，未定义意味着变量存在，但是
The difference between these two, undefined means a variable exists but
目前它没有价值。
at the moment it has no value.
它可能从来没有值，也可能曾经有值，但它没有
It may have never had a value or it might have used to have a value and it doesn't
再也没有了，但是在真空的空间里没有其他的价值，它是不确定的，对吗？
anymore but there is no other value in the vacuum of space it is undefined, right?
未声明，即使它们听起来像同义词，未声明实际上是
Undeclared even though they sound like synonyms undeclared is actually
从未在我们访问过的任何范围内正式声明。
never formally declared in any scope that we have accessed to.
这就是未申报的意思。
That's what undeclared means.
我们没有它的大理石。
We do not have a marble for it.
在严格模式下，它总是导致那些参考区域，好吗？
And in strict mode, it always results in those reference areas, okay?
保持笔直很重要。
It's important to keep those straight.
不幸的是，JavaScript试图扰乱这一点，并假装
Unfortunately, JavaScript tries to mess around with this and pretend that
UNDEFINATED与UNDEFINED和它的一些错误消息是一样的
undeclared is sort of the same thing as undefined and some of its error messages
以及其他的输出和事情，而不是从历史上看是一个非常糟糕的主意。
and other outputtings and things and not is historically a really bad idea.
我们需要将这两个概念分开。
We need to keep these two concepts separate.
有一种不同的东西是不存在的，
There's a different something being undeclared doesn't exist,
因为没有定义，所以它确实存在，但没有价值。
and being undefine definitely it does exist, but doesn't have a value.